<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<language>
	<!-- Description is from blurbsx.txt -->
	<entry name="Biogenetics" value="Biogenetics"/>
	<entry name="BiogeneticsDescription" value="We hold life to be sacred, but we also know the foundation of life consists in a stream of codes not so different from the successive frames of a watchvid. Why then cannot we cut one code short here, and start another there? Is life so fragile that it can withstand no tampering? Does the sacred brook no improvement?<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Dynamics of Mind<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SocialPsych" value="Social Psych"/>
	<entry name="SocialPsychDescription" value="If you can discover a better way of life than office-holding for your future rulers, a well-governed city becomes a possibility. For only in such a state will those rule who are truly rich, not in gold, but in the wealth that makes happiness--a good and wise life.<br/>   -- Plato,<style name='Italic'/> The Republic<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="InformationNetworks" value="Information Networks"/>
	<entry name="InformationNetworksDescription" value="The righteous need not cower before the drumbeat of human progress. Though the song of yesterday fades into the challenge of tomorrow, God still watches and judges us. Evil lurks in the datalinks as it lurked in the streets of yesteryear. But it was never the streets that were evil.<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> The Blessed Struggle<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialBase" value="Industrial Base"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialBaseDescription" value="Resources exist to be consumed. And consumed they will be, if not by this generation then by some future. By what right does this forgotten future seek to deny us our birthright? None I say! Let us take what is ours, chew and eat our fill.<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> The Ethics of Greed<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineMobility" value="Doctrine: Mobility"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineMobilityDescription" value="Once a man has changed the relationship between himself and his environment, he cannot return to the blissful ignorance he left. Motion, of necessity, involves a change in perspective.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> A Social History of Planet<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AppliedPhysics" value="Applied Physics"/>
	<entry name="AppliedPhysicsDescription" value="Scientific theories are judged by the coherence they lend to our natural experience and the simplicity with which they do so. The grand principle of the heavens balances on the razor's edge of truth.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> A History of Science<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="CentauriEcology" value="Centauri Ecology"/>
	<entry name="CentauriEcologyDescription" value="Planet's atmosphere, though a gasping death to humans and most animals, is paradise for Earth plants. The high nitrate content of the soil and the rich yellow sunlight bring an abundant harvest wherever adjustments can be made for the unusual soil conditions.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> A Comparative Biology of Planet<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="ProgenitorPsych" value="Progenitor Psych"/>
	<entry name="ProgenitorPsychDescription" value="And I stood before him, and I sang unto her, and it appeared to listen. His very countenance rippled like the sea, and the sound of my own voice came back to me, distorted. For a moment I thought she was mocking me, or it was nonsapient and mimicking me. Then I understood: the sounds were not important; it was how I affected his sounds and how she affected mine that transmitted the message.<br/>   -- Prime Function Aki Zeta-Five,<style name='Italic'/> One Future<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="PolymorphicSoftware" value="Polymorphic Software"/>
	<entry name="PolymorphicSoftwareDescription" value="Technological advance is an inherently iterative process. One does not simply take sand from the beach and produce a Dataprobe. We use crude tools to fashion better tools, and then our better tools to fashion more precise tools, and so on. Each minor refinement is a step in the process, and all of the steps must be taken.<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Looking God in the Eye<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Superconductor" value="Superconductor"/>
	<entry name="SuperconductorDescription" value="Important? Yes! Critical? Absolutely. I would go so far as to say that Superconducting Fiber alone makes our present economy possible.<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> MorganLink 3DVision Live Interview<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="NonlinearMathematics" value="Nonlinear Mathematics"/>
	<entry name="NonlinearMathematicsDescription" value="There are two kinds of scientific progress: the methodical experimentation and categorization which gradually extend the boundaries of knowledge, and the revolutionary leap of genius which redefines and transcends those boundaries. Acknowledging our debt to the former, we yearn nonetheless for the latter.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> Address to the Faculty<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AppliedRelativity" value="Applied Relativity"/>
	<entry name="AppliedRelativityDescription" value="You ivory tower intellectuals must not lose touch with the world of industrial growth and hard currency. It is all very well and good to pursue these high-minded scientific theories, but research grants are expensive and you must justify your existence by providing not only knowledge, but concrete and profitable applications as well.<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> The Ethics of Greed<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="FusionPower" value="Fusion Power"/>
	<entry name="FusionPowerDescription" value="Our ancestors harnessed the power of a sun, and so again shall we.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> The Science of Our Fathers<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SilksteelAlloys" value="Silksteel Alloys"/>
	<entry name="SilksteelAlloysDescription" value="Until quite recently, spider silk had the highest tensile strength of any substance known to man, and the name Silksteel pays homage to the arachnid for good reason.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> U.N. Scientific Survey<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedSubatomicTheory" value="Advanced Subatomic Theory"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedSubatomicTheoryDescription" value="The substructure of the universe regresses infinitely towards smaller and smaller components. Behind atoms we find electrons, and behind electrons quarks. Each layer unraveled reveals new secrets, but also new mysteries.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> For I Have Tasted The Fruit<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="HighEnergyChemistry" value="High Energy Chemistry"/>
	<entry name="HighEnergyChemistryDescription" value="At atrociously high energy states, the properties of matter change subtly and new miracles become possible. The Plasma Accretion process is now dangerous and difficult to control, but its products will soon become commonplace in our society.<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> The Lord Works<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="FrictionlessSurfaces" value="Frictionless Surfaces"/>
	<entry name="FrictionlessSurfacesDescription" value="As I stepped onto the Magtube, a thought struck me:<br/>Can there be friction where there is no substance?<br/>And can substance be tricked into hiding from itself?<br/>   -- Dr. Gayle Nambala,<style name='Italic'/> Morgan Industries Researcher<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Nanometallurgy" value="Nanometallurgy"/>
	<entry name="NanometallurgyDescription" value="Our scientists now use fractal theory to &quot;teach&quot; the molecules to assume, or resume, a particular form. Substances of amazing strength become simple once the formulae are properly computed.<br/>   -- Col. Corazon Santiago,<style name='Italic'/> The Council of War<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SuperstringTheory" value="Superstring Theory"/>
	<entry name="SuperstringTheoryDescription" value="A brave little theory, and actually quite coherent for a system of five or seven dimensions--if only we lived in one.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> Now We Are Alone<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedMilitaryAlgorithms" value="Advanced Military Algorithms"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedMilitaryAlgorithmsDescription" value="Man has killed man from the beginning of time, and each new frontier has brought new ways and new places to die. Why should the future be different?<br/>   -- Col. Corazon Santiago,<style name='Italic'/> Planet: A Survivalist's Guide<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="MonopoleMagnets" value="Monopole Magnets"/>
	<entry name="MonopoleMagnetsDescription" value="I maintain nonetheless that yin-yang dualism can be overcome. With sufficient enlightenment we can give substance to any distinction: mind without body, north without south, pleasure without pain. Remember, enlightenment is a function of willpower, not of physical strength.<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Essays on Mind and Matter<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="MatterCompression" value="Matter Compression"/>
	<entry name="MatterCompressionDescription" value="Preliminary analysis indicates that our rivals have developed a safe and reliable method to simulate conditions existing on the interior of a stellar mass. The fabrication and transmutation of materials possible in such an environment guarantees significant industrial and military applications.<br/>   -- Probe Team Operations Directorate,<style name='Italic'/> Top Secret Report<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="UnifiedFieldTheory" value="Unified Field Theory"/>
	<entry name="UnifiedFieldTheoryDescription" value="Beware, you who seek first and final principles, for you are trampling the garden of an angry God and he awaits you just beyond the last theorem.<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> But for the Grace of God<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="GravitonTheory" value="Graviton Theory"/>
	<entry name="GravitonTheoryDescription" value="This unusual specimen is not so much a classic particle as a connector--a kind of string attaching two particles. As distance increases the connective power becomes attenuated, but if it is cut the power vanishes: forever.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> For I Have Tasted The Fruit<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AppliedGravitonics" value="Applied Gravitonics"/>
	<entry name="AppliedGravitonicsDescription" value="&quot;What goes up . . . better doggone well stay up!&quot;<br/>   -- Morgan Gravitonics,<style name='Italic'/> Company Slogan<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="QuantumPower" value="Quantum Power"/>
	<entry name="QuantumPowerDescription" value="Heaven lasts long, and Earth abides<br/>What is the secret of their durability?<br/>Is it because they do not live for themselves<br/>That they endure so long?<br/>   -- Lao Tzu,<style name='Italic'/> Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SingularityMechanics" value="Singularity Mechanics"/>
	<entry name="SingularityMechanicsDescription" value="Yes, yes, we've all heard the philosophers babble about &quot;oneness&quot; being &quot;beautiful&quot; and &quot;holy&quot;. But let me tell you that THIS kind of oneness certainly isn't pretty and if you're not careful it will scare the bejeezus out of you.<br/>   -- Anonymous Lab Technician,<style name='Italic'/> MorganLink 3DVision Live Interview<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="ControlledSingularity" value="Controlled Singularity"/>
	<entry name="ControlledSingularityDescription" value="Some would ask, how could a perfect God create a universe filled with so much that is evil. They have missed a greater conundrum: why would a perfect God create a universe at all?<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> But for the Grace of God<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="TemporalMechanics" value="Temporal Mechanics"/>
	<entry name="TemporalMechanicsDescription" value="Time travel in the classic sense has no place in rational theory, but temporal distortion does exist on the quantum level, and more importantly it can be controlled.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> For I Have Tasted The Fruit<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="ProbabilityMechanics" value="Probability Mechanics"/>
	<entry name="ProbabilityMechanicsDescription" value="Einstein would turn over in his grave. Not only does God play dice, the dice are loaded.<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Looking God in the Eye<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Pre-SentientAlgorithms" value="Pre-Sentient Algorithms"/>
	<entry name="Pre-SentientAlgorithmsDescription" value="Begin with a function of arbitrary complexity. Feed it values, &quot;sense data&quot;. Then, take your result, square it, and feed it back into your original function, adding a new set of sense data. Continue to feed your results back into the original function ad infinitum. What do you have? The fundamental principle of human consciousness.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> The Feedback Principle<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SuperTensileSolids" value="Super Tensile Solids"/>
	<entry name="SuperTensileSolidsDescription" value="Optical computers, genetic catalogs, nanorepair modules--forget all of that. It's when you see a megaton of steel suspended over your head by a thread the thickness of a human hair that you really find God in technology.<br/>   -- Anonymous Metagenics Dockworker,<style name='Italic'/> MorganLink 3DVision Live Interview<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="PlanetaryNetworks" value="Planetary Networks"/>
	<entry name="PlanetaryNetworksDescription" value="If our society seems more nihilistic than that of previous eras, perhaps this is simply a sign of our maturity as a sentient species. As our collective consciousness expands beyond a crucial point, we are at last ready to accept life's fundamental truth: that life's only purpose is life itself.<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Looking God in the Eye<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DigitalSentience" value="Digital Sentience"/>
	<entry name="DigitalSentienceDescription" value="We are no longer particularly in the business of writing software to perform specific tasks. We now teach the software how to learn, and in the primary bonding process it molds itself around the task to be performed. The feedback loop never really ends, so a tenth year polysentience can be a priceless jewel or a psychotic wreck, but it is the primary bonding--the childhood, if you will--that has the most far-reaching repercussions.<br/>   -- Bad'l Ron, Wakener,<style name='Italic'/> Morgan Polysoft<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Self-AwareMachines" value="Self-Aware Machines"/>
	<entry name="Self-AwareMachinesDescription" value="Without sensibility no object would be given to us, without understanding no object would be thought. Thoughts without content are empty, intuitions without concepts are blind.<br/>   -- Immanuel Kant,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Critique of Pure Reason&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/><br/><br/>I swear sometimes they're watching me.<br/>   -- Bozon Pete, Shift Foreman,<style name='Italic'/> Metagenics Biomachinery Division<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineInitiative" value="Doctrine: Initiative"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineInitiativeDescription" value="A ship at sea is its own world. To be the captain of a ship is to be the unquestioned ruler of that world and requires all of the leadership skills of a prince or minister.<br/>   -- Col. Corazon Santiago,<style name='Italic'/> Leadership and the Sea<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineFlexibility" value="Doctrine: Flexibility"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineFlexibilityDescription" value="He held his arm too stiffly, and so was thrown back repeatedly, until at last I seized his forearm and snapped it back against itself. His training suffered while the arm healed, of course, but I felt this was a lesson he must learn early, and well.<br/>   -- Spartan Kel,<style name='Italic'/> Honing the Ki<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="IntellectualIntegrity" value="Intellectual Integrity"/>
	<entry name="IntellectualIntegrityDescription" value="Man's unfailing capacity to believe what he prefers to be true rather than what the evidence shows to be likely and possible has always astounded me. We long for a caring Universe which will save us from our childish mistakes, and in the face of mountains of evidence to the contrary we will pin all our hopes on the slimmest of doubts. God has not been proven not to exist, therefore he must exist.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> For I Have Tasted The Fruit<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SyntheticFossilFuels" value="Synthetic Fossil Fuels"/>
	<entry name="SyntheticFossilFuelsDescription" value="Fossil fuels in the last century reached their extreme prices because of their inherent utility: they pack a great deal of potential energy into an extremely efficient package. If we can but sidestep the 100 million year production process, we can corner this market once again.<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> Strategy Session<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineAirPower" value="Doctrine: Air Power"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineAirPowerDescription" value="Air Power rests at the apex of the first triad of victory, for it combines Mobility, Flexibility, and Initiative.<br/>   -- Spartan Battle Manual"/>
	<entry name="PhotonWaveMechanics" value="Photon/Wave Mechanics"/>
	<entry name="PhotonWaveMechanicsDescription" value="Time dilates as the speed of light approaches. To the extent that light consists of particles, it is in its own way timeless. Through simple perturbations of the temporal manifold, we can refract or repel photons most efficiently.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> Now We Are Alone<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="MindMachineInterface" value="Mind/Machine Interface"/>
	<entry name="MindMachineInterfaceDescription" value="The Warrior's bland acronym, MMI, obscures the true horror of this monstrosity. Its inventors promise a new era of genius, but meanwhile unscrupulous power brokers use its forcible installation to violate the sanctity of unwilling human minds. They are creating their own private army of demons.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> Report on Human Rights<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Nanominiaturization" value="Nanominiaturization"/>
	<entry name="NanominiaturizationDescription" value="Objects once measured in meters have become so small that they cannot be seen by the naked eye, with revolutionary applications across the board. Gentlemen, forget what your courtesans have told you: size does matter!<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> Morgan Industries Annual Report<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineLoyalty" value="Doctrine: Loyalty"/>
	<entry name="DoctrineLoyaltyDescription" value="Therefore a wise prince will seek means by which his subjects will always and in every possible condition of things have need of his government, and then they will always be faithful to him.<br/>   -- Niccolo Machiavelli,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;The Prince&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="EthicalCalculus" value="Ethical Calculus"/>
	<entry name="EthicalCalculusDescription" value="Some vices miss what is right because they are deficient, others because they are excessive, in feelings or in actions, while virtue finds and chooses the mean.<br/>   -- Aristotle,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Nichomachean Ethics&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialEconomics" value="Industrial Economics"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialEconomicsDescription" value="Our first challenge is to create an entire economic infrastructure, from top to bottom, out of whole cloth. No gradual evolution from previous economic systems is possible, because there IS no previous economic system. Each interdependent piece must be materialized simultaneously and in perfect working order; otherwise the system will crash out before it ever gets off the ground.<br/>   -- CEO Nwabudike Morgan,<style name='Italic'/> The Centauri Monopoly<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialAutomation" value="Industrial Automation"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialAutomationDescription" value="In the borehole pressure mines 100km beneath Planetsurface, at the Mohorovicic Discontinuity where crust gives way to mantle, temperatures often reach levels well in excess of 1000 degrees Celsius. Exploitation of Planet's resources under such brutal conditions has required quantum advances in robotic and teleoperational technology.<br/>   -- Morgan Industries, Ltd.,<style name='Italic'/> Annual Report<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="CentauriMeditation" value="Centauri Meditation"/>
	<entry name="CentauriMeditationDescription" value="The Isle of the Deep is really not a single creature but a colony of thousands of individual tubules, an aquatic vector of the Mind Worm which terrorizes Planet's continents. Over its lifetime certain tubules secrete a tough, gluelike substance which hardens to form the characteristic shell that floats the colony and creates the appearance of a rogue island.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> A Comparative Biology of Planet<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfTheHumanBrain" value="Secrets of the Human Brain"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfTheHumanBrainDescription" value="There are only two ways in which we can account for a necessary agreement of experience with the concepts of its objects: either experience makes these concepts possible or these concepts make experience possible.<br/>   -- Immanuel Kant,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Critique of Pure Reason&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="GeneSplicing" value="Gene Splicing"/>
	<entry name="GeneSplicingDescription" value="The genetic code does not, and cannot, specify the nature and position of every capillary in the body or every neuron in the brain. What it CAN do is describe the underlying fractal pattern which creates them.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> Nonlinear Genetics<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Bio-Engineering" value="Bio-Engineering"/>
	<entry name="Bio-EngineeringDescription" value="Why do you insist that the human genetic code is &quot;sacred&quot; or &quot;taboo&quot;? It is a chemical process and nothing more. For that matter -we- are chemical processes and nothing more. If you deny yourself a useful tool simply because it reminds you uncomfortably of your mortality, you have uselessly and pointlessly crippled yourself.<br/>   -- Chairman Sheng-ji Yang,<style name='Italic'/> Looking God in the Eye<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Biomachinery" value="Biomachinery"/>
	<entry name="BiomachineryDescription" value="I loved my chosen. How then to face the day when she left me? So I took from her body a single cell, perhaps to love her again.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> Time of Bereavement<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="NeuralGrafting" value="Neural Grafting"/>
	<entry name="NeuralGraftingDescription" value="I think, and my thoughts cross the barrier into the synapses of the machine, just as the good doctor intended. But what I cannot shake, and what hints at things to come, is that thoughts cross back. In my dreams, the sensibility of the machine invades the periphery of my consciousness: dark, rigid, cold, alien. Evolution is at work here, but just what is evolving remains to be seen.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> Man and Machine<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Cyberethics" value="Cyberethics"/>
	<entry name="CyberethicsDescription" value="The wicked have told me of things that delight them, but not such things as your law has to tell.<br/>   -- Saint Augustine,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Confessions&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="Eudaimonia" value="Eudaimonia"/>
	<entry name="EudaimoniaDescription" value="The happy life is thought to be one of excellence; now an excellent life requires exertion, and does not consist in amusement. If Eudaimonia, or happiness, is activity in accordance with excellence, it is reasonable that it should be in accordance with the highest excellence; and this will be that of the best thing in us.<br/>   -- Aristotle,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Nichomachean Ethics&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="TheWillToPower" value="The Will to Power"/>
	<entry name="TheWillToPowerDescription" value="Man is a rope, tied between beast and overman--a rope over an abyss. A dangerous across, a dangerous on-the-way, a dangerous looking-back, a dangerous shuddering and stopping. What is great in man is that he is a bridge and not an end: what can be loved in man is that he is an overture and a going under. I love those who do not know how to live, for they are those who cross over.<br/>   -- Friedrich Nietzsche,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Thus Spoke Zarathustra&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="ThresholdOfTranscendence" value="Threshold of Transcendence"/>
	<entry name="ThresholdOfTranscendenceDescription" value="And when he has brought forth and reared this perfect virtue, he shall be called the friend of god, and if ever it is given to man to put on immortality, it shall be given to him.<br/>   -- Plato,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;The Symposium&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="MatterTransmission" value="Matter Transmission"/>
	<entry name="MatterTransmissionDescription" value="The first living thing to go through the device was a small white rat. I still have him, in fact. As you can see, the damage was not so great as they say.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> See How They Run<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="CentauriEmpathy" value="Centauri Empathy"/>
	<entry name="CentauriEmpathyDescription" value="Observe the Razorbeak as it tends so carefully to the fungal blooms; just the right bit from the yellow, then a swatch from the pink. Follow the Glow Mites as they gather and organize the fallen spores. What higher order guides their work? Mark my words: someone or something is MANAGING the ecology of this planet.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> Planet Dreams<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="EnvironmentalEconomics" value="Environmental Economics"/>
	<entry name="EnvironmentalEconomicsDescription" value="         We sit together,<br/>        the mountain and I,<br/>  until only the mountain remains<br/>   -- Li Po,<style name='Italic'/> From the Yang Collection<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="EcologicalEngineering" value="Ecological Engineering"/>
	<entry name="EcologicalEngineeringDescription" value="The prevalence of anoxic environments rich in organic material, combined with the presence of nitrated compounds has led to an astonishing variety of underground organisms which live in the absence of oxygen and &quot;breathe&quot; nitrate. Likewise, the scarcity of carbon in the environment has forced plants to economize on its use. Thus, all our efforts to return carbon to the biosphere will encourage the native life to proliferate. Conversely, the huge quantities of nitrate in the soil will be heaven to human farmers.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> The Early Years<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="PlanetaryEconomics" value="Planetary Economics"/>
	<entry name="PlanetaryEconomicsDescription" value="The Morgans fear what may not be purchased, for a trader cannot comprehend a thing that is priceless.<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> The Collected Sermons<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdvEcologicalEngineering" value="Advanced Ecological Engineering"/>
	<entry name="AdvEcologicalEngineeringDescription" value="You are the children of a dead planet, earthdeirdre, and <br/>  this death we do not comprehend. We shall take you in, but <br/>    may we ask this question--will we too catch the planetdeath<br/>      disease?<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> Conversations with Planet<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="CentauriPsi" value="Centauri Psi"/>
	<entry name="CentauriPsiDescription" value="The Mind Worms are the natural defenses of the living Planet--the white blood cells, if you will. In a world in which unassimilated thought represents danger, the Mind Worm seeks out concentrations of sentient mental energy and destroys them, ruthlessly and efficiently.<br/>   -- Commissioner Pravin Lal,<style name='Italic'/> Mind Worm, Mind Worm<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfAlphaCentauri" value="Secrets of Alpha Centauri"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfAlphaCentauriDescription" value=" You waited so long to heed us, earthdeirdre,<br/>   Almost we pruned you, as we may yet prune your branches.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> Conversations with Planet<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfCreation" value="Secrets of Creation"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfCreationDescription" value="And when the hourglass has run out, the hourglass of temporality, when the noise of secular life has grown silent and its restless or ineffectual activism has come to an end, when everything around you is still, as it is in eternity, then eternity asks you and every individual in these millions and millions about only one thing: whether you have lived in despair or not.<br/>   -- Soren Kierkegaard,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;The Sickness Unto Death&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedSpaceflight" value="Advanced Spaceflight"/>
	<entry name="AdvancedSpaceflightDescription" value="And so we return again to the holy void. Some say this is simply our destiny, but I would have you remember always that the void EXISTS, just as surely as you or I. Is nothingness any less a miracle than substance?<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> We Must Dissent<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="HomoSuperior" value="Homo Superior"/>
	<entry name="HomoSuperiorDescription" value="Companions the creator seeks, not corpses, not herds and believers. Fellow creators the creator seeks--those who write new values on new tablets. Companions the creator seeks, and fellow harvesters; for everything about him is ripe for the harvest.<br/>   -- Friedrich Nietzsche,<style name='Italic'/> &quot;Thus Spoke Zarathustra&quot;, Datalinks<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="OrganicSuperlubricant" value="Organic Superlubricant"/>
	<entry name="OrganicSuperlubricantDescription" value="Organic Superlube? Oh, it's great stuff, great stuff. You really have to keep an eye on it, though--it'll try and slide away from you the first chance it gets.<br/>   -- T. M. Morgan-Reilly,<style name='Italic'/> Morgan Metagenics<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="QuantumMachinery" value="Quantum Machinery"/>
	<entry name="QuantumMachineryDescription" value="Men in their arrogance claim to understand the nature of creation, and devise elaborate theories to describe its behavior. But always they discover in the end that God was quite a bit more clever than they thought.<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> We Must Dissent<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="MatterEditation" value="Matter Editation"/>
	<entry name="MatterEditationDescription" value="'Abort, Retry, Fail?' was the phrase some wormdog scrawled next to the door of the Edit Universe project room. And when the new dataspinners started working, fabricating their worlds on the huge organic comp systems, we'd remind them: if you see this message, ALWAYS choose 'Retry.'<br/>   -- Bad'l Ron, Wakener,<style name='Italic'/> Morgan Polysoft<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="OpticalComputers" value="Optical Computers"/>
	<entry name="OpticalComputersDescription" value="We have reached an informational threshold which can only be crossed by harnessing the speed of light directly. The quickest computations require the fastest possible particles moving along the shortest paths. Since the capability now exists to take our information directly from photons travelling molecular distances, the final act of the information revolution will soon be upon us.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> For I Have Tasted The Fruit<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialNanorobotics" value="Industrial Nanorobotics"/>
	<entry name="IndustrialNanoroboticsDescription" value="Already we have turned all of our critical industries, all of our material resources, over to these . . . things . . . these lumps of silver and paste we call nanorobots. And now we propose to teach them intelligence? What, pray tell, will we do when these little homunculi awaken one day and announce that they have no further need of us?<br/>   -- Sister Miriam Godwinson,<style name='Italic'/> We Must Dissent<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="CentauriGenetics" value="Centauri Genetics"/>
	<entry name="CentauriGeneticsDescription" value="Remember, genes are NOT blueprints. This means you can't, for example, insert &quot;the genes for an elephant's trunk&quot; into a giraffe and get a giraffe with a trunk. There -are- no genes for trunks. What you CAN do with genes is chemistry, since DNA codes for chemicals. For instance, we can in theory splice the native plants' talent for nitrogen fixation into a terran plant.<br/>   -- Academician Prokhor Zakharov,<style name='Italic'/> Nonlinear Genetics<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SentientEconometrics" value="Sentient Econometrics"/>
	<entry name="SentientEconometricsDescription" value="The fungus has been Planet's dominant lifeform since about the time of the Lower Paleozoic on Earth. But when, once every hundred million years or so, the neural net at last achieves the critical mass necessary to become sentient, the final metamorphosis kills off most of the other life on the planet. It is possible that we humans can help to break this tragic cycle.<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> Planet Dreams<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="RetroviralEngineering" value="Retroviral Engineering"/>
	<entry name="RetroviralEngineeringDescription" value="The Academician's private residences shall remain off-limits to the Genetic Inspectors. We possess no retroviral capability, we are not researching retroviral engineering, and we shall not allow this Council to violate faction privileges in the name of this ridiculous witch hunt!<br/>   -- Fedor Petrov,<style name='Italic'/> Vice Provost for University Affairs<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="OrbitalSpaceflight" value="Satellite Reconnaissance"/>
	<entry name="OrbitalSpaceflightDescription" value="I have often been asked: if we have traveled between the stars, why can we not launch the simplest of orbital probes? These fools fail to understand the difficulty of finding the appropriate materials on this Planet, of developing adequate power supplies, and creating the infrastructure necessary to support such an effort. In short, we have struggled under the limitations of a colonial society on a virgin planet. Until now.<br/>   -- Col. Corazon Santiago,<style name='Italic'/> Planet: A Survivalist's Guide<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="FieldModulation" value="Field Modulation"/>
	<entry name="FieldModulationDescription" value="The Progenitor race appears to sense, and possibly even manipulate, local fields an untrained human cannot perceive without mechanical aid, including at the very least electricity and magnetism. This sensitivity creates entirely new worlds of artistic endeavors for the race-or it may be developed into a powerful combat awareness that can foil any attempt at surprise.<br/>   -- Prime Function Aki Zeta-Five,<style name='Italic'/> Alien Analysis<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdaptiveDoctrine" value="Adaptive Doctrine"/>
	<entry name="AdaptiveDoctrineDescription" value="War is war; destruction is destruction. You think this is obvious. But war is not destruction, it is victory. To achieve victory, simply appear to give the opponent what he wants and he will go away, or join you in your quest for additional power.<br/>   -- Datatech Sinder Roze,<style name='Italic'/> Information Burns<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="AdaptiveEconomics" value="Adaptive Economics"/>
	<entry name="AdaptiveEconomicsDescription" value="Humans : correct in making the leap from wealth as currency to wealth as energy. But logic failure : wealth ultimately is extension of desire, fluctuating with emotions and state of mind. Desires : when all are supported in purely adaptable system, true wealth is achieved.<br/>   -- Usurper Judaa Marr,<style name='Italic'/> Human : Nature<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="BioadaptiveResonance" value="Bioadaptive Resonance"/>
	<entry name="BioadaptiveResonanceDescription" value="I saw the alien phalanx coming toward us, and I calmed my mind as Kri'lan had taught me. And what I saw next to the phalanx was a shadow regiment, half-formed from the resonance around them. I cursed the aliens...with power like that, each one could fight as many, and I thanked Planet for sending us the betrayer.<br/>   -- Prophet Cha Dawn,<style name='Italic'/> The Betrayer and I<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SentientResonance" value="Sentient Resonance"/>
	<entry name="SentientResonanceDescription" value="And here we tinker with metal, to try to give it a kind of life, and suffer those who would scoff at our efforts. But who's to say that, if intelligence had evolved in some other form in past millennia, the ancestors of these beings would not now scoff at the idea of intelligence residing within meat?<br/>   -- Prime Function Aki Zeta-Five,<style name='Italic'/> The Fallacies of Self-Awareness<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfTheManifolds" value="Secrets of the Manifolds"/>
	<entry name="SecretsOfTheManifoldsDescription" value="Kri'lan taught me of the resonance and how to feel it. After much training, I could see -- the very surface under our feet, Planet itself -- is a living, fluctuating nexus of energy, violent, beautiful and quite unstable. And I could also feel its cousins -- distant mirrors on the other side of the space-time continuum -- the far-flung Manifolds.<br/>   -- Prophet Cha Dawn,<style name='Italic'/> The Betrayer and I<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="N-SpaceCompression" value="N-Space Compression"/>
	<entry name="N-SpaceCompressionDescription" value="Humans : there is no space inside rocket. Progenitor : space exists around all things with mass. Space : &quot;here&quot;. Inside rocket : &quot;there&quot;. Secret: bring here to there.<br/>   -- Caretaker Lular H'minee,<style name='Italic'/> Secret : Space<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="StringResonance" value="String Resonance"/>
	<entry name="StringResonanceDescription" value="To understand a thing is to know the manner by which it might be destroyed. A fundamental understanding of the basic building-blocks of the Universe is essential, then, to the total destruction of everything.<br/>   -- Foreman Domai,<style name='Italic'/> One Tool, One Thought<style name='Default'/>"/>
	<entry name="TranscendentThought" value="Transcendent Thought"/>
	<entry name="TranscendentThoughtDescription" value="  Eternity lies ahead of us, and behind.<br/>    Have you drunk your fill?<br/>   -- Lady Deirdre Skye,<style name='Italic'/> Conversations with Planet, Epilogue<style name='Default'/>"/>
</language>
